[♪♪♪]
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
[BELL TOLLS]
HEADMASTER:
Lights out!
WOMAN:
Cletus, are you there?
CLETUS:
My angel.
This is for you.
What did the doctor say?
He said the mutations
are advancing.
My powers are too strong.
Cletus, I'm scared.
CLETUS:
It's gonna be okay.
They're coming to take me away.
[VOICE SHAKING]
They're sending me to a place
where there are others like me.
They can't do that.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
They can't take you from me.
You're my one bright light.
I will always love you!
CLETUS:
Frances!
[GRUNTS]
FRANCES [GRUNTING]:
Get off!
Frances!
CLETUS: No! No!
[BANGING ON WINDOW]
[SIREN WAILS]
Any last words?
[INHALES, SHRIEKS]
[MUFFLED GRUNTING]
[GUN FIRES]
[EARS RINGING]
[SPEAKER BUZZES, CRACKLES]
Welcome to your new home,
Frances.
[♪♪♪]
[DISTANT SHOUTING]
[ELECTRONIC CHIME]
[AUDIO MUFFLES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
DR. PAZZO: Your old
boyfriend's finally getting
what he deserves.
And the world will be
a safer place without him.
[♪♪♪]
EDDIE: Detective Mulligan,
with all due respect,
I don't want anything to do
with Cletus Kasady.
MULLIGAN: Well, that's too bad,
because he only wants to see you.
Though, in my opinion, you had
your chance with Kasady
and you blew it.
Right, um, so...
what does he want?
Maybe he wants
to spill the beans
about where the missing bodies
are buried.
So you're gonna have to do
the right thing for a change.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[VENOM SNARLS]
VENOM:
No!
Take your tiny hands off of me!
We should be out there
protecting the city lethally!
- [VENOM SNARLS]
- [CLATTERING]
[SNARLS]
What was that?
Unhand me!
Man should never
consent to crawl
when he has
the impulse to fly.
You are a bottom-feeder.
[WHISPERS]
Be quiet.
How many times have I told you
that I want you to hide
yourself when I am working?
I am serious. It is important.
You have to show me respect.
- Respect? Respect?
- Yes. Yes.
- Okay.
Kasady gonna give you
the scoop, right?
- Right.
- Wrong.
- What do you mean?
- Because you blow everything.
Oh, okay, I see.
You're talking
about Anne again.
I miss her!
I will do it.
I don't like you.
VENOM:
Let me eat him!
You do not deserve nice things.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
CLETUS:
Welcome back, Eddie Brock.
I've been thinking about you.
What do you want, Cletus?
I mean, why am I here?
Do a man who's buried alive
a kindness, won't you?
Get a message out to all my...
fans.
And in return,
I'll give you my life.
What?
Story.
I heard the written word
hasn't been working out
so well.
Piece like this,
an exclusive...
[CLEARS THROAT]
...would put you back on top.
Go on.
People love...
serial killers.
All my secrets laid bare,
Eddie.
So much carnage.
But why me?
[LAUGHS]
I like you.
All right, it's a deal.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What's your message?
[PAPER RUSTLING]
That distant cathedral
- is all I see...
- Mm-hmm.
...fractured angel
the other part of me.
Print that in your column.
Is that it? This, um...
Who's gonna...
Who's gonna read that,
some random haiku?
Print it,
and what's mine is yours.
Wow, lucky me.
Goodbye, Eddie.
Thank you.
VENOM:
What a dick.
Eddie, look. Look.
EDDIE [WHISPERS]:
What are you doing?
VENOM:
Your job for you.
CLETUS:
Eddie.
Don't forget me, Eddie.
[COUGHS, SNIFFS]
What did you get?
Uh, I got a headache
and probably got tuberculosis.
What? A little louder.
[CHUCKLES]
He read me poetry, man.
Is this some kind of joke
to you, Eddie?
Because I'm not laughing.
VENOM: Yeah,
you could do with a laugh.
Come on, man.
These things, they just take
a little time, all right?
Well, the second
he gives you something...
Of course.
Keep me ahead of the curve,
Eddie.
- Don't embarrass me.
- All right.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- Do you understand?
EDDIE:
Trust me, the only scoop
I'm getting today
is double chocolate chip.
VENOM:
No! I get brain freeze.
[ENGINE REVS, TIRE SQUEALS]
VENOM:
Come here.
Look.
- I'm looking.
- Grab those.
All right.
Whoa. Okay.
[GRUNTING]
VENOM:
Now, what do you think?
- I think I'm Pablo Picasso.
- No!
- Okay.
- Come here. Look.
[GRUNTING RAPIDLY]
- Well, say what you see.
- Uh, it's a house.
VENOM:
Never mind.
Oh, I know this one.
- It's a tree.
- Idiot.
Sit down.
Now, pay attention.
[♪♪♪]
VENOM:
Bingo.
Holy cow.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
REPORTER: Would you say your
friendship with Cletus Kasady
is what allowed you to solve
this decades-old mystery?
You are the only person
from the outside world
he's spoken with.
Seems he likes you.
Well, you know,
he's a serial killer.
I don't see how
he can like anyone.
REPORTER [VOICE-OVER]:
Brock was able to uncover
what the FBI and police
could not.
Bowing to public outrage,
the governor of California
has overturned his moratorium
and reinstated
the death penalty for Kasady.
[SHRIEKING]
[YELLING]
Brock's career has been given
a much-needed revival,
putting him back on top
once more.
[ENGINE REVVING]
[NEWS THEME PLAYS]
REPORTER 2: A harrowing story
finally comes to an end.
Vindication for the victims
and closure for the families.
Thanks to the diligence
of one man.
- Thank you, Eddie Brock.
- VENOM: And Venom.
You know,
this could be us, Eddie.
Going out there, solving cases,
fighting bad guys.
Maybe I eat them, hmm?
And then we save the day.
EDDIE: But we saved the day.
It's done.
[YELLS]
You said I could eat bad guys!
- [SNARLING]
- This again?
I need to be free,
feeling the wind in my hair
and the sand between my toes.
You don't have any hair.
You are not listening to me.
Oh, I'm listening.
I cannot live
like this anymore.
- I'm starving.
- So eat those guys.
- VENOM: I can't.
- [CHICKENS CLUCKING]
Sonny and Cher
are best friends.
EDDIE: Are you serious?
That's ridiculous. That's what...
[YELLS, GROANS]
Man, that was abusive.
That was abuse.
[GRUNTS]
And that's a $2,000 TV.
You have got to get control
of your aggression.
That is why we have Snookie!
I cannot live on chicken
and chocolate alone.
I need brains.
Chickens have brains.
I most passionately disagree.
Look.
Look at those poor idiots.
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
Small brains.
Come on, man, it's not
their fault that you, uh...
you live on
the old phenylethyla...
- laphenylethylan.
- Phenylethylalanine.
Yeah, I just...
I just said that.
I've told you a thousand times,
- because it is only found...
- Yeah?
- ...in brains and in chocolate.
- And in chocolate.
That's right. All right,
well, how about this?
You live in my body,
you live by my rules.
- I live in your body because...
- Why?
...unfortunately,
I don't have many options.
Well, how about this, son?
The FBI is still
investigating us
for all of that stuff that
"we were involved with,"
so if one more head
goes missing,
we will get hauled off
into Area 51.
They will kill us both.
So somebody has to be
responsible.
Responsibility...
it's for the mediocre.
- Food!
- Can you stop doing that?
- Food! Food!
- Please just stop doing that now.
- Come on, stop doing that.
- Food!
- I have a deadline! Will you...
- Food...!
Goddamn it! Fine!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BELL JINGLES]
- Good evening, Eddie.
- Hey, Mrs. Chen.
- Good evening, Venom.
- [VENOM SPEAKS MANDARIN]
EDDIE:
He says hi. Oh.
MRS. CHEN:
Chocolate hasn't arrived yet.
- VENOM: No!
- Oh, no. We have a deal.
What's gonna happen?
You gonna stop protecting me?
I don't think so.
I've been keeping
my mouth shut,
- feeding your little secret.
- Wow.
Little old Mrs. Chen is
a little old blackmailer, huh?
Less of the old. I am 39.
- VENOM: And I am Barry Manilow.
- Right.
VENOM:
I am happy to eat Mrs. Chen.
No, no, you cannot eat
Mrs. Chen.
- What?
- Well, I guess it's gonna have to be plan B.
What's plan B?
- Aah! Not this again!
- [CHICKENS CLUCKING]
I need human brains to survive.
EDDIE: Uh-uh.
Now, pick up some chickens, man.
Let's go.
[GROANS]
[CHICKENS SCREECHING]
[GRUNTING]
[WHEEZING, COUGHING]
I'm done with this grossness.
Look at all the amazing things
that we can do.
We are wasting our talent.
[WOMAN WHIMPERING, GRUNTING]
Bad guy.
- VENOM: Hello, kitty.
- [GASPING, WHIMPERING]
EDDIE:
Leave him. Leave him be.
- Leave him be! Leave him be!
- [SCREAMING]
- I shall remove your head.
- EDDIE: No, you won't.
- I will use it for bowling!
- No, you will not.
VENOM:
I will take it to...
What is the one
that we like, Eddie?
EDDIE:
It's Lucky Strike.
- Yes! Lucky Strike!
- EDDIE: Put him down!
I will take you
to Lucky Strike,
and I will score
a 300-point game.
- EDDIE: You won't.
- The rest of your pudgy little
- boy body will be left here...
- [MUGGER WHIMPERING]
...rolling around
in dumpster juice.
- EDDIE: Oh, God.
- [SNARLS]
No! Put him down!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
- no, no, no, no, no, no!
- [SCREAMING]
EDDIE:
No!
VENOM:
Fine!
EDDIE:
She didn't want our help.
She did not know
she needed our help, Eddie.
There is a difference.
[PHONE RINGING]
VENOM:
It is Anne.
- Anne is on the phone, Eddie!
- [EDDIE GASPS, WHIMPERS]
Hey, Anne.
ANNE:
Hey, E-Eddie. Hi.
- Hi.
- VENOM: Be nice to her.
ANNE:
You sound out of breath.
I'm-I'm not catching you
at a bad time, am I?
No, no, not at all.
I'm just, uh...
- I'm just hanging around.
- Okay.
Uh, I'm-I'm sorry
I haven't returned your calls.
I guess...
I just needed a little space
after the whole...
alien biting a guy's
head off thing, so...
VENOM:
Ah, the good old days.
Anyway, so I have some news,
and-and I was wondering
if we could meet.
- VENOM: Yes!
- Yeah, sure, that would be, uh...
That would be fine. Great.
Okay, great.
Uh, how's tomorrow night?
Tomorrow night? Yeah, great.
- 8:00?
- L'Araignée?
- Okay, great.
- Looking forward to it.
Oh... Yeah, okay.
Me, too. Bye.
Great.
VENOM:
It's over with the doctor!
That is the voice of a woman
- who just got brutally dumped.
- [WHIMPERS]
♪ All right ♪
["HOWLIN' FOR YOU"
BY THE BLACK KEYS PLAYING]
♪ Yeah... ♪
Stop.
VENOM: Don't you want
to look your best?
Just leave me alone.
You are always nitpicking.
[QUIET CHATTER]
Wow.
[LAUGHING]
Hey.
- [LAUGHING] Okay. Hi.
- Yeah.
Wow.
VENOM:
Awkward.
So, uh, h-how's it going?
How's, uh...
- How's Mr. Belvedere? Yeah.
- Uh, good, good.
You know, he's still wiping
his ass on the carpet.
- He learned that from you.
- [CHUCKLES]
Yeah, how-how's, uh...
how's the legal aid work going?
Well, you know how much
I love an underdog, so...
Yeah. Yeah, that's why you...
put up with me
for so long, huh?
You said it.
- S-So...
- So...
VENOM:
So?
I don't know, I-I thought
it would be better
to tell you in person that...
Uh-huh.
VENOM:
No!
Wow. Oh, Anne.
Wow, that is, uh...
that is so much bigger
than the...
the one that I got you.
VENOM:
Ugh, it's gaudy.
That's Dan, right?
Doc-Doctor Dan.
Yeah, that... it's Dan.
Holy shit, Anne. Way to go.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
- VENOM: Well, I am not okay.
- Yeah.
You could just say,
"Congratulations.
I'm happy for you."
You know, like two people
who still care enough
about each other to lie
so that the other one doesn't
feel like complete shit. I...
Maybe we could do
that version of this?
No, I am...
I am happy for you, Anne.
- You know, I'm, uh...
- VENOM: No.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
VENOM:
That was going to be us, Eddie.
I, for one, would not
be inconsolable
if Dan were to fall
into traffic
and lose his head and his feet
- and all of his teeth!
- What?
What was that?
What? Nothing.
Whoa.
If I ask you a question,
do you have the ability
to tell me the truth?
You mean as in being
super happy for you
because of your engagement?
Because, I mean,
you just told me to lie,
so that's really,
really confusing.
Is Venom with you?
He's dead.
VENOM: I am.
I'm playing dead right now.
Yeah, I mean, he...
- Right.
- Okay.
Well, that's...
You just don't change, do you?
What are you talking about?
This is just a...
It's a huge shock.
Um, I'm in...
Anne, I'm in love with you.
This is a lot to process.
No, the truth is you don't
love anybody. You can't.
Commitment's just not
your thing.
All right, then, fine.
Do not marry Dan.
- Dan makes me feel safe.
- Ugh.
Okay, and you made me feel
like I was on a roller coaster.
And sometimes you just
have to know when to get off.
- Yeah, and not yak.
- VENOM: And not yak!
You know, not yak.
Yak.
ANNE:
Hey, Venom.
Take care of him, all right?
Don't let him keep
messing everything up.
VENOM: I'm going to make you cry
now, Eddie.
She will love it.
Cry. Cry.
It's a lot to process.
[GRUNTS]
Congratulations, Anne.
It's great news.
[HORN HONKING]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
VENOM:
Slow down, pal.
EDDIE:
Why?
You don't believe
in consequences.
No injuries. You fix them.
No hangovers. You mend them.
I couldn't even hurt myself
if I tried.
- [HORN HONKING]
- [TIRES SQUEALING]
VENOM: Eddie, I apologize
that I can't mend the heart.
Emotional pain,
it hits much harder,
and it lasts longer.
You just need to pull up
your big-boy pants and take it.
Yeah, well, that's easy
for you to say.
Why?
Because I'm a real boy
and you're just an amoeba.
VENOM:
I will only take that
because we are hurting
right now.
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
Don't worry, buddy.
I will get you through this.
[♪♪♪]
Do you know what always
cheers me up
in the morning, Eddie?
[CYCLING THROUGH STATIONS]
Sausages and brains.
["LET'S CALL
THE WHOLE THING OFF" PLAYING]
VENOM: ♪ I say "ee-ther"
And I say "eye-ther" ♪
♪ I say "nee-ther" ♪
♪ Ee-ther, eye-ther
Nee-ther, ny-ther ♪
♪ Let's call
The whole thing off ♪
Ow! Ow, ow. Ouch. Ow.
♪ Po-tah-toes ♪
♪ I like to-may-toes
And I like to-mah-to ♪
♪ Po-tay-toes, po-tah-toes
To-may-toes, to-mah-toes ♪
♪ Let's call
The whole thing off ♪
Cheer up, old pal.
♪ And, oh, if we call
We call the whole thing off ♪
- ♪ Then we must part ♪
- [DOG BARKING]
That's for you.
[OVER RADIO]
♪ So if I like pa-jam-as ♪
♪ And you like pa-jah-mas ♪
♪ I'll wear pa-jam-as... ♪
VENOM:
Are you pen pals with an ant?
Whoa, listen to this.
"Dearest pally pal,
"I hereby invite you to witness
"my demise,
"my final moments
"on this spinning shit wheel
that we call Earth."
CLETUS [VOICE-OVER]:
You are responsible
for bringing about the end
of Cletus Kasady.
It's only right that you hold
the door for me on my way out.
- They'll stop my heart...
- [HEART BEATING, MONITOR BEEPS]
...just like it stopped
at my birth.
[FLATLINE BEEPS]
What if Cletus Kasady
- had never been revived?
- [BABY CRYING]
He would never
have pushed Grandma
- down a flight of stairs.
- [SCREAMING]
Bye-bye, Grandma,
you puckered old sphincter.
He would never have thrown
a hair dryer
- into Mother's bathtub.
- [SCREAMING]
- [ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
- [DOG BARKING]
- Yes, Mama, I'm a bad, bad boy.
- [DOG WHIMPERS, DRILL WHIRS]
He would never have been beaten
to the brink of death
by Daddy-o
- and sent to...
- [BELL TOLLING]
St. Estes Home
for Unwanted Children.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
That circus of hell...
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[SHRIEKS]
...with one bright light.
Oh, Eddie,
we are all born into this world
through blood and pain.
Every hero has an origin story.
Your friend...
EDDIE [VOICE-OVER]:
"Cletus Kasady."
Kiss, hug, kiss, hug.
Smiley face.
Ew.
VENOM:
Nutjob.
You know, I-I should be there.
Uh, no, it's a bad idea.
I mean, I-I-I put him there.
Actually, he put himself there
when he decided to be
a complete lunatic.
Ta-da!
You know, it would be nice
just to have your support
just... I mean, just for once.
- Catsup?
- You know what I mean?
VENOM: This place is an
all-you-can-eat buffet.
Who's going to care
if I polish off
a couple of these idiots?
EDDIE: You can't be sure who is
and who is not guilty, buddy.
- VENOM: They're in prison!
- EDDIE: Yeah, but, you know,
some people take
false confessions.
They, uh... you know,
they take pleas.
We watched Making a Murderer.
You all right?
Yeah, man, I'm just practicing.
VENOM:
I am a predator, Eddie.
- Mm-hmm.
- Lions do not eat salad.
Yeah, but you're not a lion,
are you?
I mean, I see you
more of a vexatious little
pig, dog, house bat thing.
That's fine.
- VENOM: You suck.
- You suck!
- Excuse me?
- EDDIE: Yeah, wow.
I don't have
an explanation for that.
I think I just... I'm having
a panic attack, um...
Yeah, I'll sign here.
Stand two feet away
from the bars.
No touching the condemned.
Understood.
- Visitor's here.
- [DOOR OPENS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
This is a "me" thing,
not a "we" thing.
VENOM:
Everything is a "you" thing.
CLETUS: Oh, happy day for
you, Eddie Brock.
- [EDDIE SNIFFS]
- Mm, what a scoop.
The end of the Magical...
Misery Tour.
I worry for your soul.
How will you live
with the weight
of snuffing out a man's life?
I was, uh... I was hoping
maybe you could give me
a couple pointers.
[LAUGHING]
Funny little guy, aren't you?
- [BEEPS]
- VENOM: Don't need that.
My memory is outstanding.
Rude.
Consequences.
Every decision you ever make.
Who do we leave behind,
and how do we leave them?
A connubial bed, empty,
waiting in the darkness
for the rescuer
who never comes.
Because of you.
VENOM:
This guy makes zero sense.
You and I are the same.
No. No, we're not.
Twisted insides, mean daddies.
You feel like home to me,
Eddie, like family.
And really, truly,
that is all I ever wanted
in this world.
Family.
Well, killing your grandmother
and your mother
sure is a funny way
of showing it.
Anything you want to unburden
yourself with before...
...um, this happens?
Yes.
I have wishes
to bestow upon you.
VENOM:
Oh, that is kind.
I want to wish you...
this heartbreak.
VENOM:
Uh-oh. Too late.
I wish for you
to see out your days alone,
as you always have been.
VENOM:
Watch it, pal.
Wh-Where are you going
with this?
You are a cancer
to everyone
who ever loved you, Eddie.
Deceived your trusting fiancée.
And no wonder Daddy
could never look at you again
after you killed his wife,
your mother,
just by being born.
VENOM:
You son of a bitch!
No, no! No, no, no, don't!
Don't!
VENOM: Speak to my friend
again like that... I dare you!
[SCREAMING]
- Hey, hey!
- [GRUNTING]
No touching the inmate.
Hey, back up!
Eddie?
You're done.
I have tasted blood before,
my friend, and that is not it.
Eddie Brock has a big secret.
Shut up, Kasady!
[♪♪♪]
VENOM:
That may have been a mistake.
EDDIE:
Shut up.
Hey, aren't you Eddie Brock?
I don't know anymore.
VENOM:
Eddie!
EDDIE: I don't want to hear
another word out your mouth.
- VENOM: Eddie.
- I don't want to hear it.
VENOM:
Eddie, I am sorry.
EDDIE: That was his last
time on record ever.
There's no more...
any words for his victims or...
You know, they're gone.
Any clues
of outstanding bodies,
we-we've lost forever
and completely.
- VENOM: I didn't mean to.
- [BLOWS NOSE]
- You didn't mean to?
- And I said I'm sorry.
You didn't mean to,
but you did it.
I mean, you just decided...
I don't know.
[BABBLES]
That's it, you did it.
You know,
you didn't even think
that we might get caught,
we might get killed?
No, you don't think about
things like that, do you?
You just think about chickens,
you think about you,
you think about what you want,
and you think about you.
Let me remind you
of something, Eddie.
You were a loser
before I came along.
You were nothing.
I made you special.
Oh, you made me special, huh?
Well, let me tell you
something, right?
Before you came along,
I had a life.
I didn't have chickens,
all right? But I had dreams.
Yeah, I had dreams,
and I had a fiancée,
and I had a really successful
TV show!
Ah, but you destroyed all
of those things by yourself.
Yeah, but you know what?
I rebuilt my life,
and now I just want to live it.
Good night.
And how did you build
this new life?
- Hmm?
- Excuse me?
Well, who found the clue
on the wall
so you could be
this big, shiny hero?
Hmm? Who found the clue?
- Who?
- Wow.
Yeah.
No, no, no.
This is not about
being a hero for me, man.
This is about wanting
to live in peace.
D-Do you understand
what I'm talking about?
No, you don't.
You don't understand
what I'm talking about.
Okay, this is about me
wanting to live
without you whining
in my ear all the time
about eating bad guys
or, like, nagging me about Anne
or destroying my place
or destroying my life!
Do you know how lucky you are
that I chose you?
You chose me?
Buddy, I'm the only person
that took you in
when your friends kicked you
off the planet Ming Mong
'cause you are a reject!
You are a pariah.
Lethal protection, my ass.
You couldn't protect anything.
You are useless.
You couldn't get a job
down here cleaning toilets!
- [WHIMPERING IN PAIN]
- I'm sorry.
I don't know what came over me.
- Please, let me fix it.
- [BABBLES]
So I can break it again!
[SQUEALS IN PAIN]
You son of a bitch.
[GRUNTING, YELLING]
- [GROANS]
- Out!
Get out.
Take your stuff. Get out!
This is my house.
- [CLATTERING]
- No!
Keep it down up there!
[GRUNTING]
VENOM:
Get out!
[GRUNTS]
[CLATTER, GLASS BREAKING]
- [CLUCKING]
- Sonny?
You wouldn't dare!
Yeah, absolutely.
No, no, no!
- VENOM: Yeah!
- No!
I'm calling the police!
I-I am so sorry.
Show yourself.
[SNARLING]
[CHOKING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [GROANS]
- [CHICKENS CLUCKING]
You can't win!
Take a look at me.
Look at the size of you.
Puny.
How dare you?
I guess this is goodbye.
Oh, yeah.
Finally something we agree on.
- [ALARM BLARING]
- [VENOM YELLING]
What in the world?
All this crazy shit.
VENOM:
Yeah.
- [SIGHS]
- [DISTANT BANGING]
[BANGING CONTINUES]
- [LOUD BANG]
- Hmm?
- [BANGING CONTINUES]
- No. No.
No, no, no, no.
No!
VENOM:
Yeah!
EDDIE:
No!
- Yeah!
- No!
Oh, yeah.
No.
[SNARLING]
[SCREAMS]
EDDIE:
No, no, no.
I wish I never met you!
[SCREAMING]
VENOM:
Sayonara!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
WARDEN: Cletus Kasady,
you have been tried, convicted
and sentenced to death
by the state of California.
May your passing bring closure
to the victims' families,
and may you find peace
in the hereafter.
CLETUS:
Soon come chaos.
Chaos soon come.
Are those your final words?
Enjoy the show.
[CLOCK TICKING]
[TICKING STOPS]
[♪♪♪]
[BURBLING]
- [CLETUS GRUNTING RAPIDLY]
- Warden.
Something wicked...
this way comes.
[YELLING]
- WARDEN: Somebody let me out!
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [EXPLOSION]
- [GROANING]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
[PANTS, WHIMPERS]
[SCREAMS]
[♪♪♪]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
[ROARS]
- [YELLS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GROANS, YELLS]
- [SNARLS]
- [ALARM BLARING]
- [SCREECHES]
[ALARM STOPS]
[WHIMPERS, PANTS]
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[GROANING]
[YELLING, GROANING]
GUARD:
Don't move!
[SCREAMING]
[ROARS]
PRISONER:
Hey!
- [INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
- [GROWLS]
[SHOUTING, GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
Please.
I got a family.
[CHEERING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
Any last words, Warden?
Don't! Please!
[SCREAMS]
[ROARS]
♪ San Quentin, may you rot
And burn in hell ♪
♪ May your walls fall down
And may I live to tell ♪
♪ And I'll walk out
A wiser, stronger man ♪
♪ And, Warden
You tasted just like ham ♪
[♪♪♪]
[VACUUM WHIRRING]
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
You two are being evicted.
Come on, don't look at me
like that.
It was never,
never gonna work out.
All right?
[♪♪♪]
Yes.
COMMENTATOR: Just because of
how quickly he moved in...
- [SIGHS]
- ...the offensive line cannot pick him up.
REPORTER:
Breaking news.
Serial killer Cletus Kasady
is on the run...
Shit.
...as a statewide
manhunt is underway...
- Oh, shit.
- ...after last night's audacious
- escape from San Quentin Prison.
- [KNOCKING]
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
REPORTER:
It is absolutely chaos here.
We have reports
of multiple casualties.
We don't how Cletus Kasady...
- Hey.
- What, you're not dead?
No.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah, sure.
Come on in.
Uh, yeah, I was just seeing
for myself on the news.
Yeah, on a scale
of one to ten, it's 11 bad.
Reports coming
from San Quentin are,
quite frankly, bananas.
Nice TV.
W-Well, how-how did he do it?
- Yeah, how did he, indeed?
- Yeah.
That's the million-dollar
question.
And yet again, you were
his special visitor.
So, what did he tell you?
Me? Nothing. Nothing at all.
Nothing about an escape plan?
Nothing about some kind
of elaborate breakout costume?
No.
Well, how come, every time,
you seem to be at the center
of these things
and then miraculously
you know nothing about it?
Maybe I'm lucky.
Yeah, right.
You-you said, um...
[CLEARS THROAT]
...the reports coming out
of San Quentin are bananas?
What-what do...
what do you mean by "bananas"?
Remember when I asked you
a similar question...
- Uh-huh.
- ...the day you interviewed him?
Information is currency.
You of all people
should know that.
Come on.
I thought he'd come
to try to find the man
that nearly got him executed,
but I guess not.
I'd lay low if I was you.
I'll see myself out.
[SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE]
EDDIE:
Okay, think.
Think, think,
think, think, think.
What would Venom do?
He would find you
before you find me,
and he would eat your face!
Damn.
- All right.
- [RECORDER BEEPS]
CLETUS [RECORDED]:
Who do we leave behind,
and how do we leave them?
- A connubial bed, empty...
- "Connubial bed."
- ...left to rot...
- Is it marriage? What...
...waiting in the darkness for
the rescuer who never comes.
EDDIE:
I don't understand.
"That circle of hell..."
CLETUS:
Because of you.
- You and I are the same.
- "With one bright light"?
CLETUS:
Twisted insides, mean daddies.
EDDIE:
"Bright light."
CLETUS:
You feel like home to me.
- Like family.
- EDDIE: St. Estes.
[ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LIVELY CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
VENOM:
Crapola!
Another one bites the dust.
[SCREAMS, WHIMPERS]
Look at all these weirdos.
My kind of people.
- Nice costume.
- WOMAN: Hey!
Awesome work.
Greatest costume ever.
Oh, my God.
- Oh.
- Is that Japanese?
No, I made it myself.
- WOMAN: Hey.
- Who, me?
Hello, gorgeous.
Sorry, no, you're not my type.
I am out of the Eddie closet.
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hello, darlin'.
Ooh, racer red.
Got to have it.
[SIGHS]
CARNAGE:
Let's get this party started.
- [ENGINE STARTS]
- [HARD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, hell yes.
MAN:
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! Stop!
- Stop that! Stop! Stop!
- [HORNS HONKING]
Ah, shit.
- You are real.
- CARNAGE: I am.
And once I kill that thing
that made me,
we will be indestructible.
I know where to find him,
but first,
I need you to help me find
something I lost.
- Deal.
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [HORN HONKS]
♪ My soul ascended to the sky
It's just you and I ♪
♪ Gone, but I'm feeling
Too alive... ♪
Oh, yeah!
[LIVELY CHATTER, CHEERING]
Dude.
♪ I assume you'll be
Coming for blood ♪
♪ That makes two of us ♪
♪ That makes two of us
Venom... ♪
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, yeah, bro! Tight!
♪ Venom ♪
♪ Venom, venom, venom, venom ♪
♪ Follow me, follow me
Follow me ♪
♪ Actually, don't follow me
Nobody... ♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[FEEDBACK SQUEALS]
Thank you.
[CROWD MURMURING]
MAN [LAUGHING]:
Oh, yeah!
Oh, shit.
Your costume is amazing!
Thank you, one person.
[CHEERING]
Eddie was wrong.
He kept me hidden
because he was ashamed.
[MURMURING]
But look at me now.
You love me, and I'm free!
[CHEERING]
- Yeah!
- VENOM: Yeah!
Stop this cruel treatment
of aliens.
- It is wrong.
- [CHEERING]
All of us should be able
to live together
upon this ball of rock.
[CHEERING]
Yeah!
Free to be who we be!
[CHEERING]
I love you!
I love you, too.
[CHEERING]
- Yeah!
- CROWD: Yeah!
Lethal Protector out.
[MICROPHONE THUMPS,
FEEDBACK SQUEALS]
[CROWD CHEERING, WHISTLING]
Whoa, that was
a hard act to follow.
I wish you could have
seen me tonight...
[GRUNTS]
...Eddie.
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[WINGS FLUTTERING]
[DOG BARKS IN DISTANCE]
Holy shit.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Mulligan.
- Uh, it's Eddie Brock here.
Look, uh, this may be
a long shot,
but I-I think
I may have found something.
Go on, Eddie. What do you got?
Last time I spoke to Kasady,
he was talking to me
about connubial beds
and-and marriage.
And, uh, it didn't make
a whole lot of sense to me,
but, um, I'm here at St. Estes,
and I found this, uh...
Well, I'm standing
in front of a... of a...
of a tree,
and I'm-I'm looking at it.
It's, uh...
it's got a carving on it.
It says "CK loves FB."
I'm thinking that maybe
whoever this FB is
might know where he's headed.
And, uh... a-and if you can,
I don't know,
pull up some files
from St. Estes,
maybe you can figure out
who this FB is.
FB, that's, uh...
that's Frances Barrison.
Wow. That-that's quick.
Yeah, it's impossible, Eddie.
She's dead.
I, uh... I shot her.
[FRANCES INHALES DEEPLY]
[SHRIEKING]
[GUN FIRES]
[HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
[RINGING STOPS]
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[HIP-HOP PLAYING]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
♪ A living legend
Intention his name ♪
♪ Don't get distracted... ♪
- [BELL JINGLES]
- [ELECTRONIC BELL CHIMES]
Can I help you, sir?
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Got any of those internets?
[SIGHS, PANTS]
You're alive.
[♪♪♪]
[DISTANT YELLING]
When I get out, I'm gonna
slice your face off
and wear it to a party!
You're never getting out
of here, Siegfried.
[CHUCKLES]
No one does.
[BUTTON CLICKS, SPEAKER BEEPS]
Well, Frances,
it seems your sweetheart
has done a Houdini act
over there at San Quentin.
It's all over the news.
Oh, don't get excited.
He's not gonna find you.
COMPUTER VOICE:
Screw you.
How flattering.
But you're not my type.
I wonder where he could be.
COMPUTER VOICE:
I'm right here.
Ta-da.
[CLETUS LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[BUTTON CLICKS, SPEAKER BEEPS]
Hi, baby.
[FRANCES SOBS SOFTLY]
I...
don't want you
to freak out, okay?
Um, I'd like you to meet...
Carnage.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS, LAUGHS]
That is so hot.
[FRANCES LAUGHING]
[ALARM RINGING AND BLARING]
Go!
[SCREAMING, GRUNTING]
[ENGINE STARTS, REVS]
A '66.
[GASPS]
My dream car.
Yeah, I remember.
Let's see what you got.
[SIRENS BLARING]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[FRANCES SCREAMS, LAUGHS]
[CLETUS & FRANCES WHOOPING]
[FRANCES SHOUTS, LAUGHS]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
CLETUS:
Mm, mm.
[SNARLS]
Yes, baby!
[SIREN WAILING]
[ROARS]
[FRANCES WHOOPS, LAUGHS]
[WHOOPING]
[ROARS]
OFFICER [OVER SPEAKER]:
This is SFPD. Stand down.
[GROWLS]
[GLASS BREAKING,
BULLETS RICOCHETING]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[SHRIEKS]
[SQUEALS]
[YELLS]
Stop!
You'll kill him!
CARNAGE: She does that
again, I'll eat her face.
He's sensitive to sound.
OFFICER [OVER SPEAKER]:
Stop the vehicle. Stand down.
[PILOT SCREAMS]
CLETUS:
Who said romance was dead?
[♪♪♪]
Hey. No drunks in here.
[WEAKLY]
Help me. Food.
Out. You get out!
Chocolate.
Venom?
VENOM:
I'm having trouble
keeping them standing, Mrs. C.
Where's Eddie?
VENOM:
Food.
[BANGING]
Monsters!
Monsters everywhere!
They're everywhere!
- Monsters!
- [INMATES SHOUTING]
[ELECTRICAL CRACKLING]
[♪♪♪]
Put out an APB.
Form a perimeter.
Blockade state lines.
And bring in Brock.
[DOOR OPENS]
I'm no use to anybody here.
I'm just wasting your time.
Well, you know
what I keep thinking?
I keep thinking,
"What else is Eddie Brock
"not sharing
about Cletus Kasady?
"Now, why was it Eddie
that Cletus wanted
to witness the execution?" Huh?
Bad things happen around you.
Multiple dead bodies
at your building last year,
that bizarre outburst
at the lobster restaurant,
and only you
at the Life Foundation
when that rocket exploded.
And now Clyde's found Bonnie,
and there's a dead psychiatrist
at a facility
I knew nothing about
until today.
And people are talking
about seeing monsters.
Monsters?
Uh, what-what do you mean...
- what do you mean, "monsters"?
- Monsters, Eddie!
Everywhere Cletus goes,
so goes this supposed monster.
- Oh, God.
- Talk to me, Eddie.
- [EDDIE GROANS]
- Talk to me!
[SCREAMS]
MULLIGAN:
How's he doing it, Eddie?
[VOICE-OVER]
What's the secret?
How's he making people
see things?
All right, I, uh...
[SNIFFS]
I can't answer any more
of your questions
without making my phone call.
I'll get you your phone call.
But you know
what secrets want, Eddie?
They want out.
That's why they're
so hard to keep.
[DOOR OPENS]
DAN:
Eddie asked you to do this?
And he doesn't have anyone else
that can help him?
We're gonna be late
for the party.
He's in trouble, Dan.
Yeah, trouble is his thing.
Are there gonna be
aliens again?
No, of course not.
I'd like to speak to him alone.
Well, your duty of honesty
supersedes
your duty to the client
if somebody gets harmed.
They teach you that
at posh school?
Oh, hey. Anne.
Hey, Anne, thank you so...
thank you so much for coming.
[SIGHS] Boy,
that little guy's a charmer, huh?
How much do I need to worry
about you right now?
Uh, I-I messed up.
Okay. How badly?
Uh, it couldn't be worse,
and it's-it's all on me.
Whatever you did, Eddie,
you just need to tell
the cops the truth.
No. No.
No, I can't tell them
that they are chasing
a serial killer
[WHISPERING] who's also
got an alien inside of him.
And he's capable
of killing everybody.
Venom.
Talk to me. What's happening?
No, he's-he's not here.
He's not here.
Is this, like, an "I'm lying"
"He's not here,"
or is this a real
"He's not here"?
He's not here.
- ANNE: Jesus Christ, Eddie.
- [RADIO CRACKLES]
DISPATCHER [OVER RADIO]:
St. Estes fire. All units.
What the actual f...
- Eddie, think. Think.
- I don't know. I don't know.
All I know that...
i-is that he can't go long
without eating food, right,
so he's eating chicken
and he eats chocolate,
and that's it.
And that is only if he's still
observing the rules.
We need to find him.
You mean I need to find him.
Yeah, you need
to find him, please.
And then I-I... I will fix it.
- I'll try.
- Thank you.
[♪♪♪]
Mrs. Chen.
- Who's asking?
- It's me.
What do you want?
- Oh, she's a charmer.
- [SIGHS] Okay, listen.
You broke Eddie's heart.
Okay, I actually
don't have time
to explain why
that's wildly off the mark.
Do you know where Venom is?
You want to break
his heart, too?
I'm not gonna get into
who did what to who.
Eddie said that he might be
here because of the chocolate.
I-I just need to speak
with the alien.
Wha... Hey, you said there
weren't gonna be any aliens.
- I meant more aliens.
- REPORTER: Breaking news.
The mayor has issued
a curfew...
Can you turn
the volume up, please?
REPORTER: Kasady and
Barrison should be treated
as armed
and extremely dangerous.
An all-out manhunt
continues tonight.
[MUTES TV]
So?
- Cletus has a symbiote.
- DAN: Oh, my God.
Any other information you're
pathologically lying about?
- Pussy.
- Excuse me?
Eddie needs Venom.
She just called me a pussy.
He said he didn't need him,
that life was better
without him.
Okay, I don't understand.
What do you care...
Oh, wait a second.
You get out here right now.
[GASPS]
Do you... D-Do you see that?
- Seriously, do you see that?
- Yeah, hon, I've seen it.
VENOM: Eddie's going to
have to fight this battle
all by his little bitch self.
Oh, don't be a big baby.
Go help your friend.
He said I couldn't
get a job fixing toilets.
Cletus will come for him.
He won't survive without you.
Of course he won't.
Because I am the hero
of the two of us.
Yeah, you're the big sexy hero.
You're the coolest,
you're the hottest,
and you're the bravest.
I am.
You know, I'm still
standing right here.
No one likes you, Dan!
I love seeing you in action.
[GRUNTS]
Let's go save that asshole.
[♪♪♪]
[FRANCES LAUGHING]
CLETUS: I promised
we'd be free from here.
FRANCES: And we'd walk to
the cathedral on the hill.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
A wedding.
CLETUS:
Three guests.
One for each of us.
FRANCES:
The cop that took my eye.
CLETUS:
Eddie Brock.
And Venom.
A red wedding.
[DOOR OPENS]
You... you didn't find him?
OFFICER:
Oh, my Lord.
What happened?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
EDDIE:
Hey, Dan.
All right, let's go.
VENOM:
I'm not talking to him!
Well, he doesn't want
to come out.
What-what do you mean?
We-we have to leave right now
'cause Cletus is gonna
wipe the city out.
VENOM: We're not doing
shit until he apologizes.
So, he's looking for an apology.
Look, I know that amends aren't
- really your thing, but...
- EDDIE: An apology?
What, like, as in right...
right now, an apology?
VENOM:
I need him to beg.
Fine, I will be
the bigger of us.
VENOM: I will always be the bigger of
us, but go on.
What did he say?
What is he saying?
He said he's listening
very sincerely.
All right, listen to this.
I am sorry.
VENOM:
Not the right tone.
I'm sorry.
VENOM:
Nope.
I-I am sorry.
So weird.
I'm sorry!
I don't know why
you're shouting at me.
Well, 'cause...
Okay, well, fine.
I was a... I was a loser
before I met you.
- VENOM: Yep. That's right.
- And, uh...
and now I am someone.
All right? You made me special.
VENOM:
Damn right.
Why don't you put
a cherry on it?
A cherry on that? Right. Um...
I'm...
I-I am truly very sorry
for everything that I said.
- VENOM: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Everything that I did not say.
- Everything that I did, you know.
- Mm-hmm.
And probably everything
that I-I did...
I did not... I did not do.
- VENOM: Mm...
- Yeah, he's thinking.
- VENOM: Hmm...
- Come on. Come on.
- VENOM: Okay.
- Whoa.
Whoa! Oh.
Oh, no.
VENOM:
Kiss her.
Are you gonna...
are you gonna kiss me now?
- No.
- No?
ANNE: Oh, God,
I'm never doing that again.
God, well, maybe never.
I don't know.
Honestly, it's really fun.
VENOM:
If we save the day,
can we call ourselves
the Lethal Protector?
That is so '80s.
Dan, pack quickly.
Don't stay.
And if for any reason...
Fire and sound.
"Fire and sound"?
Is that a band?
- No, it's what kills them.
- EDDIE: Yeah.
Okay, look, man, I've got her.
- [GROANING]
- VENOM: Not sorry.
- ANNE: Oh...
- God, I'm so sorry.
Man, those two need some
serious couples counseling.
[ENGINE REVS, TIRES SQUEAL]
I'm pulling up to Brock's now.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Shit. Oh, my God.
Kasady, place your hands
on your head!
Which, um...
hands?
What the...
[SNARLING]
[GUN CLICKS]
We found you.
Shriek will be so pleased.
Yoo-hoo!
Brockalicious.
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
Bling-a-ling.
Now, whose finger
were you meant for?
Ah.
A nice, shiny lure
for a little fishy.
[CAT YOWLING]
Okay. Here we go, buddy.
[GRUNTING]
- [GASPS]
- Hello, Anne.
I just incapacitated
your boyfriend.
Now, he'll be okay...
with an answer about
where Eddie Brock is.
[CHUCKLING] Well,
I'm sure as shit not gonna tell you that.
It's a shame to hurt you.
[THUMPING]
Tell Brock
Cletus will make a swap.
Her head for his.
He's gonna kill you both.
Peeps have tried that already.
Botched it.
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[SIRENS WAILING]
VENOM:
They can't find him!
They are hunting us,
too, buddy.
[THUNDER CRASHES]
Come on, where are you?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, Dan. What's going on?
- Eddie, they got her.
- Huh?
- They've taken Anne!
- Calm down.
Yeah, they took her
to their wedding.
- They took her where?
- Their wedding.
- Grace Cathedral. Hurry.
- We're on our way.
All right, it looks like
we are going to a wedding.
VENOM:
Oh, will there be canapés?
You bet your ass.
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[♪♪♪]
[BREATH TREMBLING]
[WHIMPERING]
That distant cathedral
is all I see.
Fractured angel,
the other part of me.
D-Dearly beloved...
Gifts first.
Actually, traditionally...
Shut your mouth.
Father.
Baby, I got for you
what you want most.
SHRIEK:
The cop?
- CLETUS: The cop.
- [SHRIEK LAUGHS]
Continue, Father.
Dearly beloved, if anyone
objects to this marriage,
speak now
or forever hold th-their...
[DOORS BANG OPEN]
Where is she?!
[WHIMPERS]
There you are.
Death to you, Father.
No!
Not you, Father.
You, Father.
Oh, shit!
Uh, where you going?
What are you doing?
VENOM: This is much
worse than I thought.
That is a red one. Wow. Uh...
- Red one?
- We should leave immediately.
Annie will get over it.
We never liked her anyway.
So let's go.
Now?
Congratulations
to the happy couple.
We are leaving.
Eddie! Yoo-hoo.
I'll be right with you,
all right? Mm.
Okay, you need
to come out right now.
Because I am feeling super,
super vulnerable right here.
Brock's just like you?
Not for long.
[CHUCKLES]
Eddie, over here!
You need to come out right now.
I will let you eat everybody.
You can eat 'em all!
Apart from him in the robe.
You cannot eat him.
- VENOM: Promise?
- I promise.
[SNARLS]
EDDIE:
Thank you.
[ROARS]
[YELLS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[SHRIEKS]
[SQUEALING]
Baby!
Shut your mouth.
[GROWLS]
Marriage trouble already?
[ROARS]
Time to die.
EDDIE:
That's the spirit.
I mean us.
We are going to die.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
[SNARLS]
[SQUEALING]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
I-I killed you.
Well, you can't kill a ghost.
[SHRIEKS, GROANS]
You, kill him,
but keep your mouth shut.
CLETUS: Our wife knows
what she's doing.
Just turn it down.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
- Stop him.
- My cop!
[GRUNTING]
[GROWLS, HISSES]
Honeymoon over?
PRIEST [YELPS]:
Oh, God. No.
[WHIMPERING]
- [SCREAMS]
- Power up.
EDDIE:
No!
[GROWLS, ROARS]
[PAINED GRUNTING]
Mayday, Mayday, Mayday.
Cletus Kasady...
[SCREAMS]
[GROANING]
What do they say
about an eye for an eye?
[GROANS, SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SQUEALS]
Fire and sound.
Except without the sound.
[SQUEALING]
Baby!
Cletus!
[SQUEALS, ROARS]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [CARNAGE GROWLING]
[CARNAGE SQUEALS]
[CLANGS]
[SQUEALING]
[GROANING]
[BELL CLANGS]
Mano a mano, Brock.
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[BELL CLANGS]
You know how I spent
my endless days?
- [BELL CLANGS]
- [VENOM SQUEALS]
I spent them thinking about
how you only told
one side of the story.
- [CLANGS]
- [VENOM & CARNAGE SQUEAL]
You didn't write about the part
where Cletus was abused
by Mommy, Daddy and Granny!
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[CLANGS BRIEFLY]
[YELLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[GRUNTING]
[SQUEALS]
[GROANS]
You didn't tell the world
how he was a scared little boy
that no one cared about
and no one came to save!
[EDDIE GROANING]
- You never asked yourself why!
- [GROANS, SCREAMS]
That's bad journalism!
[CHOKING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Oh, happy days.
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
I'm not a crazy man,
but I am a vengeful one.
You're going to watch her die.
[WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMS]
Anne! Anne!
- [ANNE SCREAMING]
- [CARNAGE GRUNTS]
Do something!
[PANTING]
Eddie, I'm afraid
we cannot beat them.
[ANNE SCREAMING]
Baby, that's too much.
You got to stop him.
CLETUS:
What are you doing?
I'll shut her up for good.
[SCREAMING]
No, stop! You're hurting her!
[MUFFLED YELLING]
EDDIE:
Get up!
I can't.
EDDIE:
Look. Look.
They're not symbiotic.
Get away from her!
Shut up.
Get your hands off my wife!
EDDIE:
They're not a match.
We are.
EDDIE:
That's right. We are.
Together, we are...
VENOM & EDDIE:
The Lethal Protector!
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[SNARLS]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[GRUNTS]
[MUFFLED SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[ANNE WHIMPERS]
- [GROWLS]
- [SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
- [CARNAGE SHRIEKS IN PAIN]
- [ANNE SCREAMING]
- [GROANING]
- [HISSES]
Let there be carnage!
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
- [SHUDDERING]
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERS SOFTLY]
[GROANS]
- I got you. You okay?
- [GASPING]
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[LOW GROWLING]
[STRAINED GROANING]
[PANTING]
Father, one of us must die.
EDDIE [GROANING]:
We need fire.
[ROARS]
Or sound.
- [BELL CLANGS]
- [SCREAMS]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[SHRIEKS]
CARNAGE:
No!
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Holy mackerel.
[SCREAMING]
[RUMBLING]
[CARNAGE SQUEALING]
[CARNAGE SQUEALS]
[GROANS]
He did not taste good.
[♪♪♪]
I'm a killer
with or without
the monster, Eddie.
[COUGHS WEAKLY]
You know what I really wanted?
No. What was it, Cletus?
I told you,
but you weren't listening.
Well, I'm listening now.
I wanted your friendship.
I'm sorry, Cletus.
Fuck this guy.
[♪♪♪]
[SIRENS WAILING]
You in there,
get him out of here.
They're gonna come
for you both.
I know.
Hey, Anne.
Take care.
Yeah, you, too, champ.
VENOM:
Dan!
You take care, too.
Thanks.
I like you.
We totally
didn't need him, though.
Honestly, I think he was more
of a hindrance than a help.
[♪♪♪]
Monsters.
That there is Don Quixote,
and the guy next to him
is, uh, S-Sancho Panza.
They're two
very different people
who have very different takes
on the world.
D-Different ways
of doing things.
Sometimes they didn't like
each other a whole lot,
but ultimately...
they worked together to bring
out the best in each other.
VENOM:
Eddie, the time has come.
I must go alone.
It is me they want.
Yeah.
Well, my dear Sancho,
facts are the enemy of truth.
VENOM:
What does that even mean?
It means...
It means that we are...
- frien...
- VENOM: Fugitives!
Um, yeah. Yeah.
- On the run.
- That, too.
- [WAVES CRASHING]
- [SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
["LOVE WILL TEAR US APART" BY
HOT 8 BRASS BAND PLAYS QUIETLY]
Thank you
for bringing me here.
Yeah, you're welcome, buddy.
- It's beautiful, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
EDDIE: I'm sorry that we can't
do anything about the old
"wind in your hair"
situation, but...
Osho says,
when you love someone,
- you accept the whole person...
- Osho?
...with all of their defects.
"Defects." Hmm.
Nobody is perfect.
Just go back.
Go back a minute.
You telling me...
you just said that you love me.
- Um...
- You did.
Where will we go?
I don't know. I don't know.
Anywhere that needs
a Lethal Protector, I suppose.
Oh! You really meant it!
Yeah.
We will need a cape
and a mask.
No.
No, I think you got
that covered. We're good.
["LOVE WILL TEAR US APART"
CONTINUES]
♪ Love ♪
♪ Love will tear us apart
Again ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ Love will tear us apart
Again ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ Love will tear us apart
Again ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
[SONG ENDS]
♪ You weren't with me
On the cold block nights ♪
♪ Now you front row
For the spotlight ♪
♪ Now the diamonds
In the Audemars bright ♪
♪ Jets overseas
For a fire flight ♪
♪ Young... on bull... ♪
♪ And I'll ball on 'em
Bill Cartwright ♪
♪ I can shine
Through the darkness ♪
♪ I guess I always been
A star type ♪
♪ That lion in me
Made my heart fight ♪
♪ Could've been a victim
Of a opp pipe ♪
♪ Took a million wishes
Just to get to this ♪
♪ 'Cause we ain't the ones
That the cops like ♪
♪ Been so many times
God tested me ♪
♪ They only see the answers
I got right ♪
♪ They commenting
All on the blogs ♪
♪ Trying to tell me
How to live my life ♪
♪ And I waited so patiently ♪
♪ If you can take off
Don't wait for me ♪
♪ No days off
Grind faithfully ♪
♪ I keep thanking God
For saving me ♪
♪ Front line
Showcasing our bravery ♪
♪ I know that top spot
It was made for me ♪
♪ It all paid off, so we felt
The struggle so painfully ♪
♪ Now you see me
Standing in the lights ♪
♪ But you never saw
My sacrifice ♪
♪ Or all the nights
I had to struggle to survive ♪
♪ Had to lose it all
To win the fight ♪
♪ I had to fall so many times ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Now I'm
The last one standing ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Now I'm
The last one standing ♪
- ♪ Y'all say I've changed ♪
- ♪ What? Huh? ♪
- ♪ Really though? How so? ♪
- ♪ Tell me, I got ♪
- ♪ Got all this bread ♪
- ♪ What? Yeah ♪
- ♪ I'm still sour, though ♪
- ♪ What? Eh ♪
♪ I don't know, I'm a square
Peg in a round hole ♪
♪ Like a block of cheese
In a paper towel roll ♪
♪ Rocky Balboa
Never been no towel thrower ♪
♪ Even when I got
Kicked to the curb ♪
♪ Life knocked my dick
In the dirt ♪
♪ I got back up
Flipped it the bird ♪
♪ Till I earned the attention
I yearned, not to mention ♪
♪ I learned how to turn
Resentment and hurt ♪
♪ To an unquenchable thirst
In the simplest terms ♪
♪ It's revenge of the nerd
In every sense of the word ♪
♪ And, rappers, how can we be
On the same level now ♪
♪ When I got to look down
To see these clowns ♪
♪ That are on the ground
Bitch? ♪
♪ I got clouds beneath me ♪
♪ Ever since I put out the EP
To the height of 2003 me ♪
♪ You ain't see the struggle
To make it out the D ♪
♪ Because I made it
Somehow look easy ♪
♪ Now you see me
Standing in the lights ♪
♪ But you never saw
My sacrifice ♪
♪ Or all the nights
I had to struggle to survive ♪
♪ Had to lose it all
To win the fight ♪
♪ I had to fall so many times ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Now I'm
The last one standing ♪
[SONG ENDS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Maximiliano.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Estás embarazada.
¿Estás esperando un hijo mío?
[DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
VENOM:
Oh, I love this show.
EDDIE:
Yeah.
VENOM: Maximiliano's feelings
are not being validated.
Yeah, well,
he never should've kept
such an insane secret, man.
VENOM:
We all have a past, Eddie.
What, are you...
you hiding stuff from me?
VENOM:
80 billion light-years
of hive knowledge
across universes
would explode
your tiny little brain.
What-what does that
even mean, man?
VENOM: Well,
let me give you a taste, then.
Just the smallest fraction
of the things
we symbiotes have experienced.
- Okay.
- Ready, Eddie?
Yeah.
[RUMBLING, WHIRRING]
[TV AUDIO DISTORTING]
Whoa.
VENOM:
What's happening?
EDDIE:
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
VENOM:
What the hell is that?!
Oh, that's a...
that-that's just a towel.
Where are we?
- Wh-What did you do?
- It wasn't me.
J. JONAH JAMESON: Incredibly,
this shocking revelation
brought to life by yours truly
has only raised...
What? What-what...
what is this?
JAMESON:
...of Peter Parker,
aka Spider-Man,
aka the Spider Menace.
But rest assured, dear viewers,
we here at
The Daily Bugle will...
That guy...
JAMESON:
...his web of lies.
I'm J. Jonah Jameson.
Good night...
and God help us all.
Dude, what are you doing
in my room?
Uh...
I...
[SIGHS]
["VENOM REMIX"
BY LITTLE SIMZ PLAYING]
♪ In a world where
The love isn't free ♪
♪ Through the lies
And the pain and deceit ♪
♪ See, glitter ain't
Always gold ♪
♪ They want war
But we came for the peace ♪
♪ Misfits in the belly
Of the beast ♪
♪ Get ready for the rally
In the streets ♪
♪ Don't aim too high
They tell you ♪
♪ But above clouds we reach ♪
♪ I'm numb to the words
They preach ♪
♪ We listen to
The inner voice leading ♪
♪ Listen to the words
I'm speaking ♪
♪ Always for the people
Till the day I stop breathing ♪
♪ Can't take back
All the time we spent ♪
♪ Trying to make
Deep change in the world ♪
♪ How do you get them
To understand where you're at ♪
♪ When your pain isn't felt?
It's a triumph ♪
♪ The bass ain't too loud
For the room ♪
♪ We can never be silenced ♪
♪ Venom ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ My, my, if you ever heard ♪
♪ What I heard in the night
What a fright ♪
♪ They want to see us
Abandon the fight ♪
♪ We never die
We just multiply ♪
♪ Take all the rage
You been feeling inside ♪
♪ You couldn't handle
This heat if you tried ♪
♪ City to city
It's different ♪
♪ But you and I have
Similar lives ♪
♪ I got a plan
Is you coming with me? ♪
♪ There's minutes to go
I ain't watching the time ♪
♪ Alarm bells are ringing
I'm ready to roll ♪
♪ Ain't no time to chill
When my seat don't recline ♪
♪ Ain't no apologies
I'm taking off ♪
♪ And ain't nobody
Stopping me ♪
♪ You gonna do something
Or you just watching me? ♪
♪ Only I know what the fate
Of my prophecy is ♪
♪ Yeah, I know
Where I'm headin' ♪
♪ Voice is a weapon
Watch as I tell 'em ♪
♪ Venom ♪
- ♪ Venom ♪
- ♪ Venom, venom, venom ♪
♪ Or am I in my own head?
Can't tell anymore ♪
♪ Psychotic to the death
When I dig deep ♪
♪ I can never find
Nothing left, it's a mystery ♪
♪ Rage, nothin' but rage ♪
♪ Can't figure out
If I'm going insane ♪
♪ Ain't no doubt
But we show no mercy ♪
♪ So think twice
If you want to get blazed ♪
♪ Nothin' ain't nice
Round here, no games ♪
♪ I don't want to dart
Nobody in a flash ♪
♪ True, it's a stickup
Hands in the air ♪
♪ Put the money in the bag
All cash, all cash ♪
- ♪ Venom ♪
[SONG ENDS]
[♪♪♪]
["TODAY'S SPECIAL" BY CZARFACE
FEATURING FACEPULLER PLAYING]
♪ Facepuller ♪
♪ Ain't nothing common
'Bout sense ♪
♪ Yo, they walk around dense
Have an idea ♪
♪ But never execute
Or represent ♪
♪ To observe and reflect on it
Read the room, connect on it ♪
♪ Try to understand it, hit
The planet like a big bomber ♪
♪ Tectonic plates shift
Facepuller faceless ♪
♪ Tape this 'cause you are now
Eye to eye with greatness ♪
♪ Pugilist, you would need
Illusionists to fake this ♪
♪ Yeah, we back again with it ♪
♪ Quieted ten men with it ♪
♪ Eso on my grind
Working with the monster mind ♪
♪ Dotted line and sign, I'm
A killer, I will not be kind ♪
♪ I jeopardize whoever lies
Set aside your beef ♪
♪ Once the weapon's
Weaponized ♪
♪ There'll be bedlam
In the streets ♪
♪ When I put the pen to page ♪
♪ I'm like a Xenophage
On center stage ♪
♪ You hanging by a thread ♪
♪ What a tangled web
Bang your head ♪
♪ I do this by design, so many
Snacks, so little time ♪
♪ Make a move
Your brain is food ♪
♪ And I don't think
That it's a crime, Face ♪
♪ I feel the hype of my stripes
Like a shell toe ♪
♪ Stealth mode, Operation
Violate the Health Code ♪
♪ People talk about me
When I step out fresh ♪
♪ Attitude rude and brazen
Like a raven out the nest ♪
♪ Peasants drop to their knees
Like a Bendel dress ♪
♪ Now take a deep breath
And inhale death, Facepuller ♪
[RECORD SCRATCHING]
♪ Today's special ♪
[ECHOING]
♪ No medulla oblongata ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ain't nothing common
'Bout sense ♪
♪ Unbelievable ♪
♪ Facepuller ♪
♪ Creeping out the mist
Holographic myth ♪
♪ Who is he?
I plead the Fifth ♪
♪ I complement the bricks
In the Labyrinth of Doom ♪
♪ Put him in the building
He's the baddest in the room ♪
♪ Deploy the decoy, tell
Your boys we coming through ♪
♪ With the deadly melody
We bring the ruckus like Wu ♪
♪ Yo, when I apply pressure ♪
♪ I take measures
That are drastic ♪
♪ My vision board's filled with
Ninja swords and that's it ♪
♪ You're plastic
Well, I'm real ♪
♪ The author
With the best to offer ♪
♪ Step out of a flying saucer
Reciting Geoffrey Chaucer ♪
♪ This is a poetry moment
The only opponent ♪
♪ Is the voice from within
The vertigo brings the spin ♪
♪ Well, rappers say
They're moving bricks ♪
♪ Like animated Lego
But wait, though ♪
♪ False claims
Don't make your gang fuego ♪
- [RECORD SCRATCHING]
- ♪ Facepuller ♪
[SONG ENDS]